United University Professions (UUP), Oral History Project; Records apap099
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Interview Notes and Background Material, 1968-1996; Undated; 3; 0.55 cubic ft.
  - Triggs, Emily, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 76)
  - Valter, John, ca. 1989 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 77)
  - Waskshull, Samuel, 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 78-79)
  - Wendel, Mary Louise, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 80)
  - Wesnofske, Edward, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 81)
  - Whitlock, Donald, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 82)
  - Wise, Josephine, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 83)
  - Yeracaris, Constantine, 1989; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 84)
  - Ziman-Rosenblatt, Annalee, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 85)
- Administrative Files, 1989-2003; Undated; 4; 1.23 cubic ft.
  This series contains correspondence to interviewees to provide them with instructions on reviewing the transcript of their interview and the types of materials to correct, as well as release forms from the interviewees. Also included are the transcripts that were marked by the interviewees with their corrections. The correspondence is predominantly form letters. However, there is occasional correspondence specifically directed to an individual either to address concerns they raised about the transcript or to follow up regarding the status of the respective transcript and release. (Some additional correspondence with interviewees can be found in the Interview Notes and Background Materials in Series 3). Release forms and transcripts have been marked by the interviewees regarding any seals that they wished to place on their interview as well as information they wished to have deleted from the transcript, making the transcripts unavailable to researchers until the seals expires, or not at all in cases were text was deleted. Some interviewees did not return corrected copies of their transcripts. If correspondence in this series reflected the narrator's opinion and/or reservations regarding the transcript and interview, the original was placed with the interview transcript for that individual and a copy retained in this series. As noted above, access to some of the corrected narrator transcripts in this series is either permanently or temporarily restricted. All such restrictions are noted in the box and folder list.
  - Alfonsin, Edward J., Correspondence and Release, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 86)
  - Alfonsin, Edward J., Narrator's Corrected Transcript THREE PAGES SEALED PERMANENTLY, REMAINDER AVAILABLE FOR RESEARCH, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 87-88)
    As a condition ultimately granting release of his 1990 interview, Edward Alfonsin asked for the full interview to be released in 2023 but to remove one setence and one phrase appearing on tape 5 which is part of Series 1. The interview transcript, minus these two parts, was released in 2023 in accordance with his wishes. Researchers may listen to tapes 1-4 in Series 1 and read both the typed transcript (Series 2) and the corrected version (Series 4).
  - Atkins, Bruce, Correspondence and Release, 1992-1994 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 89)
  - Atkins, Bruce, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 90)
  - Budin, Morris, Correspondence and Release, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 91)
  - Budin, Morris, Narrator's Correct Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 92)
  - Burelbach, Fred, Narrator's Corrected Transcript THREE PAGES SEALED PERMANENTLY, REMAINDER AVAILABLE FOR RESEARCH, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 93)
    As a condition ultimately granting release of his 1990 interview, Fred Burelbach asked for three pages to be removed. The interview transcript, minus these three pages, was released in accordance with his wishes. Reesearchers may read both the typed transcript (Series 2) and the corrected version (Series 4) and listen to tape 10 (Series 1). The three corrected pages and tape 9 of the interview are permanently sealed.
  - Burelbach, Fred, Release, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 94)
  - Cimineli-Geerken, Diane, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 95)
  - Cimineli-Geerken, Diane Release, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 96)
  - Cozort, William, Correspondence and Release, 1993-1996 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 97)
  - Cozort, William, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 98)
  - Crary, John, Correspondence and Release, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 99)
  - Crary, John, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 100)
  - Davidson, Robert Correspondence and Release, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 101)
  - Davidson, Robert, Narrator's Correct Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 102)
  - Drescher, Nuala Correspondence and Release, 1992; 2000 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 103)
  - Drew, Joseph, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 104)
  - Drew, Joseph Release, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 105)
  - Dubois, Robert Correspondence and Release, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 106)
  - Dubois, Robert Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 107)
  - Ether, Jack Correspondence and Release, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 108)
  - Ether, Jack Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 109)
  - Form Letters, Release Form, Agreement with UUP, Human Subjects Research Approval, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 110)
  - Geerken, Henry Correspondence and Release, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 111)
  - Geerken, Henry, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 112)
  - Granger, Robert Correspondence, 1993; 1995 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 113)
  - Gutenkauf, Dorothy, Correspondence, Release and Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990-1991; 2003 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 114)
  - Hall, Robert, Correspondence, 1993; 1995 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 115)
  - Hansen, Charles, Correspondence and Release, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 116)
  - Hansen, Charles, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 117)
  - Hartmann-Wakshull, Evelyn, Correspondence, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 118)
  - Human Subject Review and Agreement between UUP and the Oral History Program, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 119)
  - Inventasch, Harvey, Correspondence and Release, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 120)
  - Inventasch, Harvey, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 121)
  - Knudsen, Doris Correspondence, 1993; 1995 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 122)
  - Lamendola, Joseph Correspondence and Release, 1993; 1995 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 123)
    General
    Release obtained in 2023.
  - Lauter, Paul, Narrator's Corrected Transcript ONE PAGE SEALED PERMANENTLY, REMAINDER AVAILABLE FOR RESEARCH, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 124)
  - Lauter, Paul, Release, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 125)
  - Link, Eugene, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 126)
  - Link, Eugene, Release, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 127)
  - Maraviglia, Frank, Correspondence, 1992; 1995 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 128)
  - Matthews, Thomas, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 129)
  - Matthews, Thomas, Release, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 130)
  - McCaffrey, Lyle, Correspondence, 1993; 1995 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 131)
  - Nelson, Malcolm A., Correspondence and Release, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 132)
  - Nelson, Malcolm A., Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 133)
  - Piccolo, Rita, Correspondence, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Potter, Janet, Correspondence and Release, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Potter, Janet, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Potter, Robert, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Potter, Robert, Release, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Puretz, Susan L., Correspondence and Release, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Puretz, Susan L., Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Ray, Frank, Correspondence and Release, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Ray, Frank, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Sanbonmatsu, Akira, Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Santelli, Charles, Correspondence and Release, 1995; 2000 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Santelli, Charles, Narrator's Corrected Transcripts SEALED PERMANENTLY, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Schaffer, D. Jo, Correspondence and Release, 1991; Undated (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Schaffer, D. Jo, Narrator's Correct Transcript, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Shank, Alan, Correspondence and Release, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Shank, Alan, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Steck, Henry, Correspondence and Release, 1991-1993 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Steck, Henry, Narrator's Corrected Transcript SEALED PERMANENTLY, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Stewart, James, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Stewart, James, Release, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Tiger, Elizabeth, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Tiger, Elizabeth, Release, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Waskshull, Samuel and Evelyn Correspondence, 1993; 1995 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Wise, Josephine, Narrator's Corrected Transcript, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Wise, Josephine, Release, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Yeracaris, Constantine, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Administrative Files), Folder 26)